//   gitQuestions
const gitQUestions = [
    {
        question: "What is Git?",
        answers: ["A version control system", "A programming language", "A web browser", " A database management system"],
        correctAnswer: "A version control system"
    },
    {
        question: "What command is used to create a new branch in Git?",
        answers: ["git push", " git checkout", "git branch", " git merge"],
        correctAnswer: "git branch"
    },
    {
        question: "How do you undo the last commit in Git?",
        answers: ["git push --force", "git commit --amend", " git reset", "git revert"],
        correctAnswer: "git commit --amend"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of the 'git clone' command?",
        answers: ["To create a new repository", "To merge two branches", "To push changes to a remote repository", "To create a local copy of a repository"],
        correctAnswer: "To create a local copy of a repository"
    },
    {
        question: "How do you discard all local changes in Git and revert to the last committed state?",
        answers: ["git push", "git reset --hard", "git checkout", "git stash"],
        correctAnswer: " git reset --hard"
    }
]

  // HTML Questions 
  const htmlQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What is the meaning of this acronym HTML?",
      answers: ["Hyper Text", "Hyper Text Markup", "Hypees Text Marup Language", "Hyper Text Markup Language"],
      correctAnswer: "Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },
    {
      question: "How do we basicaly describe HTML?",
      answers: ["Animation", "Beauty of a page", "Skeleton of a page", "none"],
      correctAnswer: "Skeleton of a page"
    },
    {
      question: "How do you create an ordered list in HTML?",
      answers: ["<ol>", "<ul>, <list>, <order>"],
      correctAnswer: "<ol>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tag is used to define a table in HTML?",
      answers: ["<table>", "<div>", "<form>", "<input>"],
      correctAnswer: "<table>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which attribute is used to specify the URL of an external JavaScript file?",
      answers: ["src", "href", "link", "script"],
      correctAnswer: "src"
    }
  ]

// CSS questions bank 
const cssQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What is the CSS property used to set the text overflow?",
      answers: ["text-overflow","overflow", "text-wrap","text-decoration"],
      correctAnswer: "text-overflow"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Css property used to set border width?",
      answers: ["border-width" ,"width", "border", "border-size"],
      correctAnswer: "width"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Css property is used to set background-image?",
      answers: ["image", "background-image", "background", "background-picture"],
      correctAnswer: "background-image"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Css property is used to set the opacity of an element?",
      answers: ["opacity", "transpency", "translucent", "none"],
      correctAnswer: "opacity"
    },
    {
      question: "Which property is used to set the font-family of an element in css?",
      answers: ["font", "font-size", "text-front", "font-family"],
      correctAnswer: "font-family"
    }
  ]

//   JavaScript Questions
  const jsQuestions = [
    {
       question: "What is JavaScript primarily used for?",
       answers: ["Styling web pages", "Creating interactive elements on web pages", "Storing and retrieving data", "Executing server-side code"],
       correctAnswer: "Creating interactive elements on web pages"
    },
    {
        question: "Which keyword is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
        answers: ["var", "let", "const", "all of the above"],
        correctAnswer: "all of the above"
    },
    {
        question: "Which built-in method can be used to convert a string to lowercase in JavaScript?",
        answers: ["toLowerCase()", "convertToLower()", "lowerCase()", "makeLowerCase()"],
        correctAnswer: "toLowerCase()"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct way to add comments in JavaScript?",
        answers: ["// This is a comment", " <!-- This is a comment -->", "/* This is a comment */", "// This is a comment //"],
        correctAnswer: "// This is a comment"
    },
    {
        question: "What will be the result of the following expression: 5 + '5' ?",
        answers: ["10", "55", "5 + '5'", "'5' + 5"],
        correctAnswer: "55"
    }
  ]

